maddentips.com 2012-06-25

# Prima Games Site Security and Privacy Policy - Prima Games

Date of Last Revision:  October 24th, 2011

The policies below are applicable to the primagames.com website (however accessed and/or used), whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise, and other interactive features, applications or downloads that are operated by us or our affiliates and vendors and that are available through this website (the "Prima Games Site"). Prima Games is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of users of its interactive products and services. Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for users, and in particular, ensure that kids' information is protected. If you don't find your concern addressed here, feel free to contact us by e-mail at feedback@primagames.com or phone 800-733-3000.

**What Personal Information Do We Collect?**

Personal information is information that identifies you and may be used to contact you on-line or off-line. Prima Games only collects personal information from our online visitors on a voluntary basis and only during (1) contests (registration or claiming a prize), (2) during customer support or technical service requests, (3) registration for specific services, (4) marketing surveys and e-mail campaigns, (5) registration for membership on the Prima Games Site, or (6) when you order products (such as eGuides) from us online. Information collected may include your name, e-mail address, phone number, home address, birth date and credit card information. We do not require personal information for you to obtain access to the Prima Games Site; however, you will not be able to access areas that require registration without providing personal information.

In addition to the use of personal information to operate the Prima Games Site, Prima Games may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by Prima Games or shared with third parties. This collective data helps us determine how our customers use parts of the Prima Games Site, so we can improve our web site and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. We also provide statistical "ratings" information to our Prima Games partners about how our users collectively use the Prima Games Site. We do this so they too can understand how people use their areas of the Prima Games Site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience as well. This information is also used to generate advertising rates. Generally this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies" "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.

Whatever the purpose may be, we will only collect information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives.

**Information We Ask About You**

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested. You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for the product or service. We also may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the Internet, but you may always choose whether to respond or not.

**Policies for Children Under 13**

Safeguarding the personal information of children is extremely important to us. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the site. No information should be submitted to or posted on the Prima Games Site by children under 13 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, Prima Games does not knowingly collect or provide any personally identifying information of children under 13 years of age, regardless of its source, for any purpose whatsoever. Prima Games may, however, collect certain personally identifying information to protect the integrity of the web site and the safety of children under 13 using the Web site. In the event Prima Games collects such information, the information will be deleted from the Prima Games systems as soon as possible. We do not use any information collected from users under 13 years of age for any marketing or promotional purpose whatsoever. We do not allow children under 13 years of age to be listed in any member directories or to receive direct marketing communications from Prima Games or other third parties.

We assume that if you are legally providing us with credit card information, you are an adult or are otherwise authorized to do so. In no event however, should you make a purchase if you are under age 13. We're sorry, but you will need to ask your parent to make the purchase for you.

There are a number of emerging standards in the area of children's privacy that will affect how we process a child's personal information in the future. We are monitoring these changes and will redesign our systems in order to comply with these new requirements.

**Parents and Guardians**

We encourage you to get involved with your children's online usage and to be aware of the activities in which they are participating. We also ask you to check back here regularly to see what our latest policies are, particularly those relating to children.

You should be aware that if your children voluntarily disclose their names, e-mail addresses or other information on bulletin boards or chat areas of other Web sites, such disclosures may result in unsolicited messages from other parties. We suggest that you discourage your child from providing such information on this site or elsewhere unless you are confident that the information will not be misused.

**Use of Cookies**

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. "Cookies" make web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you're at our Web site. The use of "Cookies" is standard in the Internet industry, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. For example, by showing how and when guests use the site, "Cookies" help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Web site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. This information is most easily tracked with "Cookies." "Cookies" in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept "Cookies." If you prefer, you can set yours to refuse "Cookies" or to alert you when "Cookies" are being sent. However, it is possible that some areas of the Web site, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

**How We Do Not Use Cookies**

The Prima Games Web site never uses "Cookies" to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a "Cookie." Except as described in this Security and Privacy Policy, Prima Games does not use information transferred through "Cookies" for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties other than our fulfillment and service companies that help us provide a specific service to you. We do not use Cookies" to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping and contest registration (where a "Cookie" allows you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time). You may occasionally get "Cookies" from our advertisers. We do not control these "Cookies," and these "Cookies" are not subject to our "Cookie" policy. The use of advertising "Cookies" sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry.

**How We Use the Information**

We only use your personal information for the purposes stated. In addition, we may use your personal information to track your User Submissions (as defined in the Terms of Use) to be applied towards your “Prima Points” and to allow you to view your history of such submissions through the Prima Games Site, communicate with you about our products and services, to solicit information from you via our web site’s performance, your registration, and to enforce the Terms of Use and our other policies.  We also may display your user name to other community members of the Prima Games Site through the community elements of your registration. Except as disclosed in this privacy policy, Prima Games does not disclose information about your individual visits to the Prima Games Site or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number, to any outside companies (other than fulfillment and service companies that help us provide a specific service to you, e.g. distribution of our eGuides). Prima Games does not sell any customer lists or e-mail addresses. We contract with certain trusted companies to act on our behalf by performing such functions as fulfilling orders, delivering packages, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. Those entities are provided with only the information needed to perform the specific function and they may not use such information for other purposes. However, we may partner with businesses to provide special services to our customers. For example, we may offer discount coupons for services or related products. In many cases these discounts would be an added benefit to you. Prima Games may also permit use of your personal information to allow other companies to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. If Prima Games proposes to permit such use of your personal information, you will be provided an opportunity to instruct Prima Games not to allow such contact. You may contact us at any time in order to direct us to remove your information from future mailings.

Prima Games may also disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is (a) required by law or comply with legal process served on Prima Games or the Prima Games Site; (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of Prima Games, the Prima Games Site or the users of Prima Games, and (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of our guests, the Prima Games Site or the public.

**Links to Other Sites**

Users should be aware that when you are on the Prima Games Site you could be directed to other web sites that are beyond our control. There are links on our web site that take you to other web sites outside our service. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" takes you off the Prima Games Site. These links include links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use Prima Games' logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via forums or chat - that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Prima Games strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Prima Games and web sites that carry the Prima Games brand, and not to other companies' or organizations' web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked Prima Games and these branded web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies.

**Security Policy**

The importance of security for all personal information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Personal information collected by the Prima Games Site is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In many instances, such as in the case of credit card numbers and all on-line purchases, the personal information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access, each having signed confidentiality agreements. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.

**Chat Rooms, Forums and Message Boards**

In addition to directly providing information to Prima Games, you might also provide personal information through chat sessions, e-mail exchanges, forums or message boards made available to you on the Prima Games Site. This Security and Privacy Policy does not cover this type of transfer of your personal information. You should always be careful when distributing your personal information in this manner. And remember that online chat sessions and newsgroup use is considered public and you are legally responsible for your actions in these areas.

**Assignment**

Prima Games may change its ownership or corporate organization while providing the Web site and services. As a result, please be aware that Prima Games may transfer your information to another company that is affiliated with Prima Games or with which Prima Games has merged.

**Changes**

Prima Games is committed to maintaining its position as a premier site on the Internet. As our site continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Web site. In the event that these additions affect our Security and Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Security and Privacy Policy each time you use our Web site in case you missed our notice of changes to the Security and Privacy Policy.

**Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of the Prima Games Security and Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use the Prima Games Site. Your continued use of the Prima Games Site and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Correcting and Updating Information**

Prima Games also permits you to correct or update personally identifiable information that you have previously provided to us. To do so, send e-mail to: [webmaster@primagames.com](mailto:webmaster@primagames.com) indicating the information that you wish to be corrected or updated.

**Opt-Out Procedures**

You always may opt-out of receiving future mailings. The Prima Games Site provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about you. To remove your personally identifiable information from our database, to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service, send e-mail to [webmaster@primagames.com](mailto:webmaster@primagames.com) with the word "remove" in the subject line.

**Questions**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to [feedback@primagames.com](mailto:feedback@primagames.com).

**For Non-United States Users**

If you are located outside the United States, you should be aware that your personal identifiable information will be transferred to the United States, the laws of which may be deemed to have inadequate data protection. If you are located in a country outside the United States and voluntarily submit personal information to us, you thereby “opt in” and consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such personal information as provided in this privacy policy and to the transfer of that personal information to, and/or storage of that information in the United States.
